A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1982-1986, RG 37 FA1504
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1982-1986, RG 37
1962-1994
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, David (1915-2017)
Rockefeller, Laurance Spelman (1910-2004)
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich) (1908-1979)
Rockefeller, John D., III (John Davison) (1906-1978)
Mauze, Abby Rockefeller (1903-1976)
FA1504
327.55 Cubic Feet 857 containers
Arrangement
Original order. Alphabetical, in 38 series, primarily by subject/topic.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research in accordance with the terms of donation from the David Rockefeller Estate, January 2019. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Researchers interested in accessing audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
Scope and Contents
The 1982-1986 general files chronicle management of the philanthropic affairs of the third generation of the Rockefeller family primarily David Rockefeller and Laurance S. Rockefeller.
Over the years the Rockefeller family has been involved in virtually all aspects of modern philanthropy at the local, national and international levels through their foundation activities as well as their individual personal giving. Major interests include: physical and mental health, conservation, education, international relations, politics, population, religion, social welfare, the visual and performing arts, cultural exchange programs, and economic and social development of underdeveloped areas.
The general files primarily consist of correspondence, reports, pamphlets, memoranda, charters and certificates of incorporation, minutes and meeting records as well as documentation of contributions, finance and investment materials, real estate, newspaper clippings, diaries, notebooks, calendars, audio tapes, and printed material.
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1982-1986; 37; 327.55 Cubic Feet 857 containers
  Scope and Contents note
  Some 1977-1981 material may be found in these files.
  - A, 1982-1986; 1; 1.52 Cubic Feet 4 letter document boxes
    - A - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture - A-Q (Box 1, Folder 2-4)
    - Agriculture - P-Z (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture - American Farmland Trust (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Agriculture - Center for Rural Studies (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Agriculture - Institute for Food and Development Policy (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Agriculture - The Land Institute (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture - Land Stewardship Project (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Agriculture - Rural America (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Agriculture - Rural Coalition (Box 3, Folder 4, Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Arbor Acres Farm, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Arts, 1982-1986; 2; 27.42 Cubic Feet 66 letter document boxes and 5 legal document boxes
    - Arts - A-Z, 1
      - Arts - A-Am (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Arts - An-C (Box 5, Folder 1-4)
      - Arts - D-N (Box 6, Folder 1-4)
      - Arts - O-S (Box 7, Folder 1-4)
      - Arts - T-Z (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
      - American Council for the Arts (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - American Crafts Council (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - American Federation of the Arts (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Arkansas Arts Center (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Artisans Cooperative, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - ArtsConnection (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Association for Business Sponsorship of the Arts (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Business Committee for the Arts (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Century Association (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Children's Art Carnival (Box 9, Folder 6, Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Children's Art Carnival - Contributions (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - The Creo Society (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Cultural Council Foundation (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Franklin Furnace Archive, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Nancy Hanks Center (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - The Institute for Art and Urban Resources, Inc. (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Henry Klumb Memorial Committee (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts (Box 11, Folder 5, Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Printed Matter (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - MacDowell Colony, Inc. (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Municipal Art Society of New York (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - National Academy of Design (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - New York Council on the Humanities (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - New York Foundation for the Arts (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - New York State Council on the Arts (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Performing Arts for Crisis Training (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Princess Grace Foundation (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Public Art Fund, Inc. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Dance, 2
      - Dance - A-F (Box 14, Folder 5-6)
      - Dance - G-Z (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
      - Dance Theatre of Harlem, Inc. (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - School of American Ballet (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - School of American Ballet - Printed Matter (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Films, 3
      - Films - A-C (Box 16, Folder 2-4)
      - Films - C-H (Box 17, Folder 1-4)
      - Films - H-O (Box 18, Folder 1-4)
      - Films - P-Z (Box 19, Folder 1-3)
      - Accord Research and Educational Association (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Blue Ridge Productions (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Documentary Guild (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Film Arts Foundation (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - The Film Fund, 1982-1986 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - The Film Fund, 1977-1981 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Fund for Theatre and Film, 1980-1986 (Box 21, Folder 2-3)
      - The Future Wave (Box 21, Folder 4-5)
      - Ideal Communications, Inc. (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Independent Documentary Group, 1979-1986 (Box 22, Folder 2-3)
      - Nuclear Forum (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Sopher, Sharon (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Galleries, 4
      - Galleries - A-Z (Box 23, Folder 2-3)
      - The Katonah Gallery (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Libraries, 5
      - Libraries - A-Z (Box 24, Folder 1-4)
      - Lyndon Bains Johnson's Library (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - New York Public Library (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - New York Public Library - Contributions (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
      - New York Public Library - Annual Reports (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Pierpont Morgan Library (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Memorials, 6
      - Memorials (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Museums, 7
      - Museums - A (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Museums - B-H (Box 27, Folder 1-3)
      - Museums - I-Q (Box 28, Folder 1-4)
      - Museums - R-Z (Box 29, Folder 1-3)
      - Academy of Natural Sciences of Philadelphia, 1982-1984 (Box 29, Folder 4, Box 30, Folder 1-3)
      - Academy of Natural Sciences of Philadelphia - Contributions (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Academy of Natural Sciences of Philadelphia - Meetings (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Academy of Natural Sciences of Philadelphia - Printed Matter (Box 30, Folder 6, Box 31, Folder 1-2)
      - American Association of Museums (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - American Museum of Natural History (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Buffalo Bill Historical Center (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Frick Collection (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Wendell Gilley Museum of Bird Carving, 1979-1986 (Box 32, Folder 4-5)
      - The Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Independent Curators Incorporated (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Israel Museum (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Contributions (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - The Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Michael C. Rockefeller Wing (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Michael C. Rockefeller - Printed Matter (Box 34, Folder 3, Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Lila Acheson Wallace Fund (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Printed Matter (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Museum of the City of New York (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Museum of the American Indian-Heye Foundation (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
      - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, MA (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, MA - Printed Matter (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Museum of Modern Art - A-Z (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Board of Trustees (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Condominium (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Contributions, 1982-1986 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Contributions, 1972-1981 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Contributions - David Rockefeller, 1974-1987 (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Contributions - John D. Rockefeller 3rd and Blanchette Rockefeller, 1972-1987 (Box 38, Folder 3-4)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Contributions - Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1972-1982 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Fund Raising - 50th Anniversary Campaign, 1978-1983 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Printed Material (Box 39, Folder 3, Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Museum of New Mexico (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - National Building Museum (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Portland Museum of Art, Maine (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Rockwell Museum (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - The Phillips Collection (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
      - San Antonio Museum (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Smithsonian Institution - A-N (Box 41, Folder 4-6)
      - Smithsonian Institution - N-Z (Box 42, Folder 1-2)
      - Smithsonian Institution - Printed Matter (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Smithsonian Institution - Smithsonian National Associates (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - South Street Seaport Museum - A-L (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - South Street Seaport Museum - M-Z (Box 43, Folder 1-2)
      - South Street Seaport Museum - Board of Trustees (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - South Street Seaport Museum - Contributions (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - South Street Seaport Museum - Finances, 1982-1985 (Box 44, Folder 1-2)
      - South Street Seaport Museum - Fund Raising (Box 44, Folder 3-4)
      - South Street Seaport Museum - Fund Raising - A-Z (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - South Street Seaport Museum - Legal (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - South Street Seaport Museum - Minutes-Meetings (Box 45, Folder 3-4)
      - South Street Seaport Museum - Minutes/Meetings - Nominating Committee (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - South Street Seaport Museum - Printed Material (Box 46, Folder 1-2)
      - South Street Seaport Project (Box 46, Folder 3-4)
      - South Street Seaport Museum - Laurance S. Rockefeller (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - United States Holocaust Memorial Museum (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Whitney Museum of American Art (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Music, 8
      - Music - A-C (Box 47, Folder 4-5)
      - Music - D-M (Box 48, Folder 1-3)
      - Music - N-Z (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
      - "American Hymns", 1977-1981 (Box 49, Folder 3, Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Boston Symphony Orchestra, Inc. (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Brooklyn Academy of Music (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Caramoor Center for Music and the Arts, Inc. (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - The Cantata Singers, Inc. (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Carnegie Hall Society (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Carnegie Hall Society - Clippings (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - Chamber Music Society of Lincoln Center (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Grand Teton Music Festival (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Metropolitan Opera Association (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - Philharmonic-Symphony Society of New York (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Young Audiences (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Young Concert Artists (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund for Music (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund for Music - Close Down (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Paintings, 9
      - Paintings - A-Z (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
    - Poetry, 10
      - Poetry - A-Z (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Publications, 11
      - Publications - A (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - Publications - B-F (Box 54, Folder 1-3)
      - Publications - G-L (Box 55, Folder 1-3)
      - Publications - M-S (Box 56, Folder 1-4)
      - Publications - T-Z (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Africa News Service, Inc., 1977-1986 (Box 57, Folder 2-3)
      - Center for Investigative Reporting, 1982-1986 (Box 58, Folder 1-4, Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Center for War-Peace Studies (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - Committee to Protect Journalists (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Mother Jones (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Pacific News Service (Box 60, Folder 2-3)
      - Reader's Digest - A-Z (Box 61, Folder 1-3)
      - Reader's Digest - Board of Directors (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Reader's Digest - Board of Directors - LSR (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - Reader's Digest - Finances, 1982-1986 (Box 62, Folder 3-5)
      - Reader's Digest - George V. Grune (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - Reader's Digest - Printed Material (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Reader's Digest - Minutes-Meetings (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - Reader's Digest - Minutes-Meetings - Executive - Finance Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Reader's Digest - Minutes-Meetings - Executive - Finance Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - Renewable Energy News (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Ruder, Finn and Rotman (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Sopher, Sharon S., 1982-1984 (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - South End Press (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - South-North News Service (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - Acknowledgement of Books - A-Z (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Restorations, 12
      - Restorations - A-C (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Restorations - D-Z (Box 66, Folder 1-3)
      - The Custom House, 1973-1983 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Essex Institute (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Friends of Olana, Inc. (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Gracie Mansion Conservancy (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Hudson River Sloop Clearwater, Inc. (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - Middleton Place (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Mount Vernon (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - New York Landmarks Conservancy (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Statue of Liberty-Ellis Island Foundation (Box 68, Folder 4, Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Versailles Foundation, 1979-1986 (Box 69, Folder 2-3)
    - Sculpture, 13
      - Sculpture - A-Z (Box 70, Folder 1-2)
    - Theater, 14
      - Theater - A (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - Theater - B-O (Box 71, Folder 1-4)
      - Theater - P-Z (Box 72, Folder 1-2)
      - Creative Theater for Children (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - American Academy of Dramatic Arts (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - American Repertory Theater Company (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - The Mirror Theatre (Box 73, Folder 1-4, Box 74, Folder 1-2)
      - New York Shakespeare Festival (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Aviation, 1982-1986; 1.61 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes and 1 legal box
    - Aviation - A-Z (Box 74, Folder 4-5)
    - Eastern Airlines - A-Z (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Eastern Airlines (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Eastern Airlines - Annual Reports (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Eastern Airlines - LSR - Investments (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Eastern Airlines - Board of Directors - LSR (Box 76, Folder 1-2)
    - Eastern Airlines - Clippings (Box 76, Folder 3-4)
    - Eastern Airlines - Merger, 1986 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Eastern Airlines - Publicity - Texas Air (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Eastern Airlines - Sale (POC Notes) (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - B-C, 1982-1986; 4; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - B - Miscellaneous (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - C - Miscellaneous (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Joseph W. Canzeri, 1977-1984 (Box 78, Folder 1-2)
  - Civic, 1982-1986; 5; 11.96 Cubic Feet 29 letter document boxes and 2 legal document boxes
    - Civic - A-Z, 1
      - Civic - A-C (Box 78, Folder 3-4)
      - Civic - D-M (Box 79, Folder 1-3)
      - Civic - N-Z (Box 80, Folder 1-4)
      - Allegheny Conference On Community (Box 81, Folder 1)
      - American Citizenship Education Project (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - American Civil Liberties Union Foundation (Box 81, Folder 3-4)
      - Better Government Association (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - Billings, Montana (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Center for Constitutional Rights, Inc. (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Center for Constitutional Rights, Inc. - Contributions (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - Center For National Security Studies (Box 83, Folder 1)
      - Center For Responsive Politics (Box 83, Folder 2)
      - Chambers Of Commerce - A-Z (Box 83, Folder 3)
      - Citizen Action (Box 84, Folder 1)
      - Citizen Heritage Center (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - Citizens Leadership Foundation (Box 84, Folder 3)
      - Citizens Participation Project (Box 84, Folder 4)
      - Community Resource Center, Inc. (Box 85, Folder 1)
      - Conference/Alternative State and Local Polices (Box 85, Folder 2-3)
      - Connecticut Citizen Action Group (Box 85, Folder 4)
      - CORO Foundation (Box 85, Folder 5)
      - Council of Municipal Performance (Box 86, Folder 1)
      - Inform, Inc. (Box 86, Folder 2)
      - League Of Women Voters (Box 86, Folder 3)
      - League Of Women Voters of the City Of New York (Box 86, Folder 4)
      - League Of Women Voters Education Fund (Box 86, Folder 5, Box 87, Folder 1)
      - National Academy of Public Administration (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - National Emergency Civil Liberties Committee Foundation (Box 87, Folder 3)
      - National Let Them Eat Cake Sale (Box 87, Folder 4)
      - National Training and Information Center (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - New York Civil Liberties Union Foundation (Box 88, Folder 1)
      - New York Public Interest Research Group and Center, 1982-1986 (Box 88, Folder 2-3)
      - OAHU Development Conference (Box 88, Folder 4)
      - Partners For Livable Places (Box 89, Folder 1)
      - People For The American Way (Box 89, Folder 2-4)
      - People For The American Way - Contributions (Box 90, Folder 1)
      - People For The American Way - Printed Matter (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - Savannah Landmark Rehabilitation Project (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - Southwest Voter Registration (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - Urban Institute (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - New York City, 2
      - New York City - A-C (Box 91, Folder 2-4)
      - New York City - D-Z (Box 92, Folder 1-3)
      - Bronx Frontier Development Corporation (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - Bronx 2000 (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - Citizens Budget Commission (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - Citizens Committee for New York City (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - Citizens Housing and Planning Council of New York City, Inc. (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - Community Council of Greater New York (Box 93, Folder 5)
      - Harlem Restoration Project (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - Neo/Research Energy Foundation, Inc. (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - New York Board of Trade, Inc. (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry - General (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry - A-Z (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry, 1982-1983 (Box 95, Folder 1-2)
      - New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry - Business Marketing Department, 1981-1983 (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - New York Chamber of Commerce - Printed Material (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - New York City (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - New York City Office Of The Comptroller (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - New York City Partnership - A-M (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - New York City Partnership - N-Z (Box 97, Folder 1-3)
      - New York City Partnership - Contributions (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - New York City Partnership - Finances (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - New York City Partnership - Fundraising - A-Z (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - New York City Partnership - Fundraising - David Rockefeller Accounts (Box 98, Folder 2-3)
      - New York City Partnership - Fundraising - Advertising Industry, 1982-1983 (Box 98, Folder 4)
      - New York City Partnership - Fundraising - Consulting Firms, 1983 (Box 98, Folder 5)
      - New York City Partnership - Fundraising - Corporate, 1982-1983 (Box 99, Folder 1)
      - New York City Partnership - Fundraising - Entertainment Industry, 1982 (Box 99, Folder 2)
      - New York City Partnership - Fundraising - Foundations and Government, 1982-1983 (Box 99, Folder 3)
      - New York City Partnership - Fundraising - Investment Bankers, 1982-1984 (Box 99, Folder 4)
      - New York City Partnership - Fundraising - Lawyers, 1982-1984 (Box 99, Folder 5-6)
      - New York City Partnership - Fundraising - Leadership Grants, 1982 (Box 99, Folder 7)
      - New York City Partnership - Fundraising - Real Estate Industry, 1981-1982 (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - New York City Partnership - Macchiarola, Frank (Box 100, Folder 2-3)
      - New York City Partnership - Metropolitan Transit Authority, 1983-1984 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - New York City Partnership - New York State - Meetings with the Governor and Members of Legislature, 1986 February (Box 100, Folder 5)
      - New York City Partnership - Policy Committee - Minutes-Meetings, 1982-1983 (Box 101, Folder 1)
      - New York City Partnership - Printed Matter (Box 101, Folder 2)
      - New York City Partnership - Public Safety Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 101, Folder 3)
      - New York City Police Foundation, Inc. (Box 101, Folder 4)
      - NonProfit Coordinating Committee (Box 102, Folder 1)
      - Regional Plan Association (Box 102, Folder 2)
      - Settlement Housing Fund (Box 102, Folder 3)
      - Volunteer Consulting Group (Box 102, Folder 4)
      - Westway (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - Westway - Clippings (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - New York State, 3
      - New York State - A-Z (Box 103, Folder 3)
      - Franklin Delano Roosevelt Centennial Commission (Box 104, Folder 1-2)
      - Temporary Commission on the Restoration of the Capital (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - United States Government, 4
      - Bicentennial - A-Z (Box 103, Folder 4)
      - United States Government (Box 104, Folder 4)
      - Bi-Partisan Appeal on the Budget Situation (Box 105, Folder 1)
      - Government Accountability Project, 1982-1983 (Box 105, Folder 2-3)
      - Government Accountability Project, 1985-1986 (Box 106, Folder 1-4, Box 107, Folder 1)
      - Committee on the Constitutional System (Box 107, Folder 2)
      - Presidents Commission on Executive Exchange, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 3)
      - Presidents Commission on Executive Exchange, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 1-2)
      - President's Commission on Industrial Competitiveness (Box 108, Folder 3)
      - Presidents Task Force on International Private Enterprise (Box 108, Folder 4)
      - Senate Subcommittee on Immigration and Refugee Policy (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Clubs, 1982-1986; 6; 1.99 Cubic Feet 4 letter document boxes and 1 legal document box
    - Clubs - A-R (Box 109, Folder 1-4)
    - Clubs - S-Z (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Camp Fire Club Of America (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Cosmos Club (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Harbor Club (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Hemisphere Club (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Kebo Valley Club (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Lakota Club (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Links Golf Club (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - New York Yacht Club (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Knickerbocker Club, 1977-1983 (Box 111, Folder 2-3)
    - The River Club (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Sleepy Hollow Country Club (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - University Club (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Wings Club, 1977-1986 (Box 112, Folder 2-3)
    - Woodstock Golf and Tennis Club (Box 112, Folder 4)